howtostartanllc.com 2019-07-07

# Privacy Policy | How to Start an LLC

Howtostartanllc.com recognizes that its visitors, users, and others value their privacy. This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on howtostartanllc.com. The Really Useful Information Company LLC ("TRUIC") - The owner of howtostartanllc.com provides this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using howtostartanllc.com.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to TRUIC's Terms of Use. Your use of howtostartanllc.com and any personal information you provide on howtostartanllc.com remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.

Please note that any file, video, image, or other content posted at the direction of Users onto howtostartanllc.com becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.

## The Information TRUIC Collects

* * *

### User Provided Information

You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to TRUIC when choosing to participate in various activities on howtostartanllc.com such as Business Plan Generator, Business Model Canvas, downloading Free Legal Forms or posting feedback and comments, and signing up for the Newsletter.

### Cookies Information

When you visit howtostartanllc.com, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. TRUIC uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of howtostartanllc.com may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

### Log File Information

When you use howtostartanllc.com, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

## The Way TRUIC Uses Information

* * *

If you submit personally identifiable information (name and email) to us through howtostartanllc.com, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of howtostartanllc.com.

Any business information that you disclose when using Business Tools such as the Business Plan Generator and Business Model Canvas remains private. This is not considered personally identifiable information and we do not use the information given at any time. 

TRUIC does not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. TRUIC may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major howtostartanllc.com changes or for customer service purposes).

TRUIC uses both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of howtostartanllc.com and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends.

TRUIC uses cookies to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit howtostartanllc.com; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.

## When TRUIC Discloses Information

* * *

TRUIC provides personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. TRUIC requires that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

TRUIC does not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

TRUIC does share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on howtostartanllc.com.

TRUIC may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant.

TRUIC also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that TRUIC believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our web site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of TRUIC, our Users or others.

## Your Choices

* * *

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through howtostartanllc.com, in which case TRUIC may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your personal profile information at any time by visiting your account profile page.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times.

Please contact the TRUIC Team with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your personal information, your consent, or your opt-in or opt-out choices using our contact form.

## Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

* * *

TRUIC allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within howtostartanllc.com. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on howtostartanllc.com. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

TRUIC does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. The advertiser may use information regarding your use of howtostartanllc.com, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks (see links below) for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. TRUIC's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

Currently, TRUIC has relationships with the following third-party affiliate/ad networks:

## Our Commitment to Data Security

* * *

TRUIC uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. TRUIC cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to TRUIC and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, TRUIC makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

If TRUIC learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. TRUIC may post a notice on howtostartanllc.com if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us using our contact form.

## Our Commitment To Childrens' Privacy

* * *

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, TRUIC does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on howtostartanllc.com from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access howtostartanllc.com at any time or in any manner. If TRUIC learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on howtostartanllc.com without verified parental consent, then TRUIC will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

## Special Note to International Users

* * *

howtostartanllc.com is hosted in the United States and is intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If you are a User accessing howtostartanllc.com from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of howtostartanllc.com, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and our Terms of Use. You are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

## In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy

* * *

In the event that TRUIC is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

## Changes and updates to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the "effective date" below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when we received the personal information you provided. Your continued use of howtostartanllc.com constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions.

For revisions to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of the personal information you have already provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information.

Contact Information: Please contact TRUIC with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy using the contact form.
